<dashboard theme="dark">
  <label>Windows Forensic Analysis - Landing Page</label>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
      Available evidence files:
      </html>
      <table>
        <search>
          <query>index=virtuoso_plaso
| stats earliest(_time) as "Earliest Event:", latest(_time) as "Latest Event:" count by evidence_file
| fieldformat "Earliest Event:"=strftime('Earliest Event:', "%c")
| fieldformat "Latest Event:"=strftime('Latest Event:', "%c")</query>
          <earliest>0</earliest>
          <latest></latest>
        </search>
        <option name="count">10</option>
        <option name="drilldown">none</option>
      </table>
    </panel>
  </row>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
                <a id="to_top"/>
        SANS Digital Forensics "Evidence of..." Categories:
            <table style="width:100%" border="2">
          <tr>
            <th>
              <a href="#File_Download_Link" style="color:DarkOrchid;">File Download</a>
            </th>
            <th>
              <a href="#Program_Execution_Link" style="color:red;">Program Execution</a>
            </th>
            <th>
              <a href="#Deleted_File_Link" style="color:grey;">Deleted File or Knowledge</a>
            </th>
            <th>
              <a href="#Network_Activity_Link" style="color:orange;">Network Activity / Physical Location</a>
            </th>
          </tr>
          <tr>
            <th>
              <a href="#File_Folder_Link" style="color:LimeGreen;">File/Folder Opening</a>
            </th>
            <th>
              <a href="#Account_Usage_Link" style="color:LightGray;">Account Usage</a>
            </th>
            <th>
              <a href="#External_Device_Link" style="color:DodgerBlue;">External Device / USB Usage</a>
            </th>
            <th>
              <a href="#Browser_Usage_Link" style="color:DarkOrange;">Browser Usage</a>
            </th>
          </tr>
        </table>
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
                <a id="File_Download_Link"/>
                <hr style="border:2px solid DarkOrchid;"/>
                <div style="text-align:center;font-style:bold;color:DarkOrchid;font-size:175%">File Download</div>
                <br/>
                <table style="width:100%" border="2">
                    <tr>
                        <th>
                            <font color="DarkOrchid">Forensic Item:</font>
                        </th>
                        <th>
                            <font color="DarkOrchid">Description:</font>
                        </th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrchid">
                                <center>Open/Save MRU</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>In the simplest terms, this key tracks files that have been opened or saved within a Windows shell dialog box. This happens to be a big data set, not only including web browsers like Internet Explorer and Firefox, but also a majority of commonly used applications</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrchid">
                                <center>Email Attachments</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The email industry estimates that 80% of email data is stored via attachments. Email standards only allow text. Attachments must be encoded with MIME/base64 format.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrchid">
                                <center>Skype History</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Skype history keeps a log of chat sessions and files transferred from one machine to another</li>
                                <li> This is turned on by default in Skype installations</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrchid">
                                <center>Browser Artifacts</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Not directly related to “File Download”. Details stored for each local user account. Records number of times visited (frequency). </li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrchid">
                                <center>Downloads</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Firefox and IE has a built-in download manager application which keeps a history of every file downloaded by the user. This browser artifact can provide excellent information about what sites a user has been visiting and what kinds of files they have been downloading from them. </li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrchid">
                                <center>ADS Zone.Identifier</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Starting with XP SP2 when files are downloaded from the “Internet Zone” via a browser to a NTFS volume, an alternate data stream is added to the file. The alternate data stream is named “Zone.Identifier.” </li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <a href="#to_top" style="white;">back to top</a>
            </html>
    </panel>
    <panel>
      <html>
                <a id="Program_Execution_Link"/>
                <hr style="border:2px solid red;"/>
                <div style="text-align:center;font-style:bold;color:red;font-size:175%">Program Execution</div>
                <br/>
                <table style="width:100%" border="2">
                    <tr>
                        <th>
                            <font color="red">Forensic Item:</font>
                        </th>
                        <th>
                            <font color="red">Description:</font>
                        </th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="red">
                                <center>UserAssist</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>GUI-based programs launched from the desktop are tracked in the launcher on a Windows System.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="red">
                                <center>Windows 10 Timeline</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Win10 records recently used applications and files in a “timeline” accessible via the “WIN+TAB” key.  The data is recorded in a SQLite database.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="red">
                                <center>Recent Apps</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>GUI Program execution launched on the Win10 system is tracked in the RecentApps key</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="red">
                                <center>Shim Cache</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>  Windows Application Compatibility Database is used by Windows to identify possible application compatibility challenges with executables.</li>
                                <li>  Tracks the executables file name, file size, last modified time, and in Windows XP the last update t.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="red">
                                <center>Jump Lists</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>  Windows Application Compatibility Database is used by Windows to identify possible application compatibility challenges with executables.</li>
                                <li>  Tracks the executables file name, file size, last modified time, and in Windows XP the last update time.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="red">
                                <center>Amcache.hve</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>ProgramDataUpdater (a task associated with the Application Experience Service) uses the registry file Amcache.hve to store data during process creation</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="red">
                                <center>System Resource Usage Monitor (SRUM)</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Records 30 to 60 days of historical system performance. Applications run, user account responsible for each, and application and bytes sent/received per application per hour.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="red">
                                <center>BAM/DAM</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Windows Background Activity Moderator (BAM)</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="red">
                                <center>Last Assisted MRU</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Tracks the specific executable used by an application to open the files documented in the OpenSaveMRU key. In addition, each value also tracks the directory location for the last file that was accessed by that application. Example: Notepad.exe was last run using the <b>C:\%USERPROFILE%\</b>
                </li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <a href="#to_top" style="white;">back to top</a>
            </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
                <a id="Deleted_File_Link"/>
                <hr style="border:2px solid grey;"/>
                <div style="text-align:center;font-style:bold;color:grey;font-size:175%">Deleted File or Knowledge</div>
                <br/>
                <table style="width:100%" border="2">
                    <tr>
                        <th>
                            <font color="grey">Forensic Item:</font>
                        </th>
                        <th>
                            <font color="grey">Description:</font>
                        </th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="grey">
                                <center>XP Search - ACMRU</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>You can search for a wide range of information through the search assistant on a Windows XP machine. The search assistant will remember a user’s search terms for filenames, computers, or words that are inside a file. This is an example of where you can find the “Search History” on the Windows system.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="grey">
                                <center>Thumbcache</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Thumbnails of pictures, office documents, and folders exist in a database called the thumbcache. Each user will have their own database based on the thumbnail sizes viewed by the user (small, medium, large, and extra-larger)</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="grey">
                                <center>Thumbs.db</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Hidden file in directory where images on machine exist stored in a smaller thumbnail graphics.  thumbs.db catalogs pictures in a folder and stores a copy of the thumbnail even if the pictures were deleted.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="grey">
                                <center>IE | Edge file://</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>A little-known fact about the IE History is that the information stored in the history files is not just related to Internet browsing.  The history also records local and remote (via network shares) file access, giving us an excellent means for determining which files and applications were accessed on the system, day by day.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="grey">
                                <center>Search - WordQueryWheel</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Keywords searched for from the START menu bar on a Windows 7 machine</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="grey">
                                <center>Win 7/8/10 Recycle Bin</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The recycle bin is a very important location on a Windows file system to understand. It can help you when accomplishing a forensic investigation, as every file that is deleted from a Windows recycle bin aware program is generally first put in the recycle bin.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="grey">
                                <center>Last-Visited MRU</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Tracks the specific executable used by an application to open the files documented in the OpenSaveMRU key. In addition, each value also tracks the directory location for the last file that was accessed by that application.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="grey">
                                <center>center&gt;XP Recycle Bin</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>The recycle bin is a very important location on a Windows file system to understand.  It can help you when accomplishing a forensic investigation, as every file that is deleted from a Windows recycle bin aware program is generally first put in the recycle bin. </li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <a href="#to_top" style="white;">back to top</a>
            </html>
    </panel>
    <panel>
      <html>
                <a id="Network_Activity_Link"/>
                <hr style="border:2px solid orange;"/>
                <div style="text-align:center;font-style:bold;color:orange;font-size:175%">Network Activity / Physical Location</div>
                <br/>
                <table style="width:100%" border="2">
                    <tr>
                        <th>
                            <font color="orange">Forensic Item:</font>
                        </th>
                        <th>
                            <font color="orange">Description:</font>
                        </th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="orange">
                                <center>Timezone</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Identifies the current system time zone.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="orange">
                                <center>Cookies</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Cookies give insight into what websites have been visited and what activities may have taken place there.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="orange">
                                <center>Network History</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Identify networks that the computer has been connected to</li>
                                <li> Networks could be wireless or wired</li>
                                <li> Identify domain name/intranet name</li>
                                <li> Identify SSID</li>
                                <li> Identify Gateway MAC Address</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="orange">
                                <center>WLAN Event Log</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> 11000 – Wireless network association started</li>
                                <li> 8001 – Successful connection to wireless network</li>
                                <li> 8002 – Failed connection to wireless network</li>
                                <li> 8003 – Disconnect from wireless network</li>
                                <li> 6100 – Network diagnostics (System log)</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="orange">
                                <center>Browser Search Terms</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>  Windows Application Compatibility Database is used by Windows to identify possible application compatibility challenges with executables</li>
                                <li>  Tracks the executables file name, file size, last modified time, and in Windows XP the last update time</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="orange">
                                <center>System Resource Usage Monitor (SRUM)</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>  Windows Application Compatibility Database is used by Windows to identify possible application compatibility challenges with executables</li>
                                <li>  Tracks the executables file name, file size, last modified time, and in Windows XP the last update time</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <a href="#to_top" style="white;">back to top</a>
            </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
                <a id="File_Folder_Link"/>
                <hr style="border:2px solid LimeGreen;"/>
                <div style="text-align:center;font-style:bold;color:LimeGreen;font-size:175%">File/Folder Opening</div>
                <br/>
                <table style="width:100%" border="2">
                    <tr>
                        <th>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">Forensic Item:</font>
                        </th>
                        <th>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">Description:</font>
                        </th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">
                                <center>Open/Save MRU</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>In the simplest terms, this key tracks files that have been opened or saved within a Windows shell dialog box. This happens to be a big data set, not only including web browsers like Internet Explorer and Firefox, but also a majority of commonly used applications.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">
                                <center>Recent Files</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Registry Key that will track the last files and folders opened and is used to populate data in “Recent” menus of the Start menu. </li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">
                                <center>Jump Lists</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> The Windows 7 task bar (Jump List) is engineered to allow users to “jump” or access items have frequently or recently used quickly and easily.  This functionality cannot only include recent media files; it must also include recent tasks. </li>
                                <li> The data stored in the AutomaticDestinations folder will each have a unique file prepended with the AppID of the association application and embedded with LNK files in each stream.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">
                                <center>Shell Bags</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>  Which folders were accessed on the local machine, the network, and/or removable devices.  Evidence of previously existing folders after deletion/overwrite.  When certain folders were accessed.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">
                                <center>Shortcut (.LNK) Files</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Shortcut Files automatically created by Windows:<br/>- Recent Items<br/> -  Opening local and remote data files and documents will generate a shortcut file (.lnk)</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">
                                <center>Prefetch</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Increases performance of a system by pre-loading code pages of commonly used applications. Cache Manager monitors all files and directories referenced for each application or process and maps them into a .pf file. Utilized to know an application was executed on a system.</li>
                                <li> Limited to 128 files on XP and Win7</li>
                                <li> Limited to 1024 files on Win8-10</li>
                                <li> (exename)-(hash).pf</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">
                                <center>Last-Visited MRU</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Tracks the specific executable used by an application to open the files documented in the OpenSaveMRU key. In addition, each value also tracks the directory location for the last file that was accessed by that application.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">
                                <center>IE | Edge file://</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>A little known fact about the IE History is that the information stored in the history files is not just related to Internet browsing.  The history also records local, removable, and remote (via network shares) file access, giving us an excellent means for determining which files and applications were accessed on the system, day by day.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LimeGreen">
                                <center>Office Recent Files</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>MS Office programs will track their own Recent Files list to make it easier for users to remember the last file they were editing.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <a href="#to_top" style="white;">back to top</a>
            </html>
    </panel>
    <panel>
      <html>
                <a id="Account_Usage_Link"/>
                <hr style="border:2px solid LightGray;"/>
                <div style="text-align:center;font-style:bold;color:LightGray;font-size:175%">Account Usage</div>
                <br/>
                <table style="width:100%" border="2">
                    <tr>
                        <th>
                            <font color="LightGray">Forensic Item:</font>
                        </th>
                        <th>
                            <font color="LightGray">Description:</font>
                        </th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LightGray">
                                <center>Last Login</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Lists the local accounts of the system and their equivalent security identifiers.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LightGray">
                                <center>Last Password Change</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Lists the last time the password of a specific local user has been changed.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LightGray">
                                <center>RDP Usage</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Track Remote Desktop Protocol logons to target machines.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LightGray">
                                <center>Services Events</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Analyze logs for suspicious services running at boot time</li>
                                <li> Review services started or stopped around the time of a suspected compromise</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LightGray">
                                <center>Logon Types</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Logon Events can give us very specific information regarding the nature of account authorizations on a system if we know where to look and how to decipher the data that we find.  In addition to telling us the date, time, username, hostname, and success/failure status of a logon, Logon Events also enables us to determine by exactly what means a logon was attempted. </li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LightGray">
                                <center>Authentication Events</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Authentication mechanisms</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="LightGray">
                                <center>Success/Fail Logons</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Determine which accounts have been used for attempted logons. Track account usage for known compromised accounts.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <a href="#to_top" style="white;">back to top</a>
            </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
                <a id="External_Device_Link"/>
                <hr style="border:2px solid DodgerBlue;"/>
                <div style="text-align:center;font-style:bold;color:DodgerBlue;font-size:175%">External Device/USB Usage</div>
                <br/>
                <table style="width:100%" border="2">
                    <tr>
                        <th>
                            <font color="DodgerBlue">Forensic Item:</font>
                        </th>
                        <th>
                            <font color="DodgerBlue">Description:</font>
                        </th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DodgerBlue">
                                <center>Key Identification</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Track USB devices plugged into a machine.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DodgerBlue">
                                <center>First/Last Times</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Determine temporal usage of specific USB devices connected to a Windows Machine.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DodgerBlue">
                                <center>User</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Find User that used the Unique USB Device. </li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DodgerBlue">
                                <center>PnP Events</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> When a Plug and Play driver install is attempted, the service will log an ID 20001 event and provide a Status within the event.  It is important to note that this event will trigger for any Plug and Play-capable device, including but not limited to USB, Firewire, and PCMCIA devices.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DodgerBlue">
                                <center>Volume Serial Number</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>  Discover the Volume Serial Number of the Filesystem Partition on the USB. (NOTE: This is not the USB Unique Serial Number, which is hardcoded into the device firmware.)</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DodgerBlue">
                                <center>Drive Letter and Volume Name</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Discover the last drive letter of the USB Device when it was plugged into the machine</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DodgerBlue">
                                <center>Shortcut (.LNK) Files</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Shortcut files automatically created by Windows: <br/>- Recent Items <br/>- Open local and remote data files and documents will generate a shortcut file (.lnk)</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <a href="#to_top" style="white;">back to top</a>
            </html>
    </panel>
    <panel>
      <html>
                <a id="Browser_Usage_Link"/>
                <hr style="border:2px solid DarkOrange;"/>
                <div style="text-align:center;font-style:bold;color:DarkOrange;font-size:175%">Browser Usage</div>
                <br/>
                <table style="width:100%" border="2">
                    <tr>
                        <th>
                            <font color="DarkOrange">Forensic Item:</font>
                        </th>
                        <th>
                            <font color="DarkOrange">Description:</font>
                        </th>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrange">
                                <center>History</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Records websites visited by date and time. Details stored for each local user account. Records number of times visited (frequency). Also tracks access of local system files.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrange">
                                <center>Cookies</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Cookies give insight into what websites have been visited and what activities may have taken place there.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrange">
                                <center>Cache</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> The cache is where web page components can be stored locally to speed up subsequent visits</li>
                                <li> Gives the investigator a “snapshot in time” of what a user was looking at online<br/>-  Identifies websites which were visited <br/>-  Provides the actual files the user viewed on a given website  <br/>-  Cached files are tied to a specific local user account  <br/>-  Timestamps show when the site was first saved and last viewed</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrange">
                                <center>Flash + Super Cookies</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Local Stored Objects (LSOs), or Flash Cookies, have become ubiquitous on most systems due to the extremely high penetration of Flash applications across the Internet. They tend to be much more persistent because they do not expire, and there is no built-in mechanism within the browser to remove them. In fact, many sites have begun using LSOs for their tracking mechanisms because they rarely get cleared like traditional cookies.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrange">
                                <center>Session Restore</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Automatic Crash Recovery features built into the browser.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                    <tr>
                        <td>
                            <font color="DarkOrange">
                                <center>Google Analytics Cookies</center>
                            </font>
                        </td>
                        <td>
                            <ul>
                                <li> Google Analytics (GA) has developed an extremely sophisticated methodology for tracking site visits, user activity, and paid search.  Since GA is largely free, it has a commanding share of the market, estimated at over 80% of sites using traffic analysis and over 50% of all sites.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </td>
                    </tr>
                </table>
                <a href="#to_top" style="white;">back to top</a>
            </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
</dashboard>
